<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Bing: ADNOC</title>
        <link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=ADNOC</link>
        <description>Search results</description>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.bing.com:80/s/a/rsslogo.gif</url>
            <title>ADNOC</title>
            <link>http://www.bing.com:80/search?q=ADNOC</link>
        </image>
        <copyright>Copyright © 2024 Microsoft. All rights reserved. These XML results may not be
            used, reproduced or transmitted in any manner or for any purpose other than rendering
            Bing results within an RSS aggregator for your personal, non-commercial use. Any other
            use of these results requires express written permission from Microsoft Corporation. By
            accessing this web page or using these results in any manner whatsoever, you agree to be
            bound by the foregoing restrictions.</copyright>
        <item>
            <title>Maximum Energy Minimum Emissions - ADNOC</title>
            <link>https://www.adnoc.ae/</link>
            <description>We are making today’s energy cleaner, while investing in the clean energies
                of tomorrow. With sustainability at its core, our lower carbon solutions are
                delivering maximum energy with minimum emissions, as we help progress a responsible
                and realistic energy transition.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon., 24 Jun. 2024 09:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ADNOC Wallet | Customer Service Portal</title>
            <link>https://smart.adnocdistribution.ae/</link>
            <description>ADNOC Wallet login. Select your account type: Individual/Beneficiary.
                Register your Individual Wallet Now!</description>
            <pubDate>Tue., 25 Jun. 2024 12:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Careers at ADNOC Group | ADNOC Group jobs</title>
            <link>https://jobs.adnoc.ae/</link>
            <description>Explore Your Future. We give you the tools you need to discover your
                perfect job match, and the freedom and support to take your career to the next
                level.</description>
            <pubDate>Tue., 25 Jun. 2024 01:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Abu Dhabi National Oil Company - Wikipedia</title>
            <link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abu_Dhabi_National_Oil_Company</link>
            <description>Website. www .adnoc .ae. The Abu Dhabi National Oil Company ( Arabic: شركة
                بترول أبو ظبي الوطنية ), known by its acronym ADNOC, is the state-owned oil company
                of the United Arab Emirates (UAE). It is the world's 12th largest oil company by
                production. [2]</description>
            <pubDate>Tue., 25 Jun. 2024 09:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Consumer - ADNOC Distribution</title>
            <link>https://www.adnocdistribution.ae/</link>
            <description>ADNOC Distribution produces and blends top-grade lubricants at our
                state-of-the-art facilities in Abu Dhabi to the highest international standards from
                world-renowned murban crude oil. We offer a wide range of premium products across
                automotive, industrial, marine and speciality.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon., 24 Jun. 2024 21:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ADNOC Announces Comprehensive 2030 Sustainability Goals as it Extends ...</title>
            <link>
                https://www.adnoc.ae/en/news-and-media/press-releases/2020/adnoc-announces-comprehensive-2030-sustainability-goals-as-it-extends-its-legacy</link>
            <description>As part of its sustainability goals, ADNOC plans to decrease its greenhouse
                gas (GHG) emissions intensity by 25 percent by 2030, strengthening its position as
                one of the least carbon-intensive oil and gas companies in the world.</description>
            <pubDate>Fri., 21 Jun. 2024 06:41:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Who We Are - ADNOC - Abu Dhabi National Oil Company</title>
            <link>https://www.adnoc.ae/en/our-story/who-we-are</link>
            <description>Founded in 1971, ADNOC is a leading diversified energy group, wholly owned
                by the Abu Dhabi Government. Our network of fully integrated businesses operates
                across the energy value chain, helping us to responsibly meet the demands of an
                ever-changing energy market.</description>
            <pubDate>Sun., 23 Jun. 2024 20:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ADNOC Group | LinkedIn</title>
            <link>https://www.linkedin.com/company/adnocgroup</link>
            <description>At ADNOC, we’re accelerating deployment of AI and digital technologies from
                the board room to the control room – shaping and enhancing our approach to
                efficiency, sustainability and safety.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon., 15 Aug. 2022 12:53:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ADNOC Drilling - Drilling</title>
            <link>https://adnocdrilling.ae/</link>
            <description>At the core of the Abu Dhabi National Oil Company’s (ADNOC) upstream
                activities and the sole provider of drilling rig services in the Emirate of Abu
                Dhabi, ADNOC Drilling is the strategic enabler of ADNOC Group’s current and future
                oil and gas production programs.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon., 24 Jun. 2024 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ADNOC Supplier Hub - Abu Dhabi National Oil Company</title>
            <link>https://supplierhub.adnoc.ae/landing</link>
            <description>Enabling suppliers to go beyond procurement. Our all-in-ADNOC platform
                delivers end-to-end solutions for streamlined management across procurement, legal,
                health and safety, finance, and more.</description>
            <pubDate>Mon., 24 Jun. 2024 13:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>